{
    "id": "e2a5bdd914be4767a6da359e219d968f",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I waited for him …………………. 7 o’clock and then I went home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "till",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "29d8e85a422a4623933df2bacea72e59"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will make a cake ………………… I have time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "when",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "971dd1cb78c9489abf76fa92236f17b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "They had left ………………… the time I reached their place.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "before",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "10fa7b27ee4f40838995807720b64656"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. the teacher left the classroom, the students started chatting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "No sooner",
                "Hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "17f7cfa83beb46ad95b373c1e08c32b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will call you ……………….. I leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "till",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5ad05623ab174f279132d53bb3834724"
        },
        {
            "question": "Take this bag with you …………………. you leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "after",
                "before",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "96ca3b16b8514bcbaa55c4583fa540eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was depressed ………………….. she didn’t know what to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "70927e16398d4b9098d11daab5f7cb1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We must reach there ………………… he leaves.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "until",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f06d88734c0e432caef3cf37e55fca9a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I cut myself …………………. I was shaving.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "whenever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b0e4c36e0de949079a23efb61a4a97b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "We cancelled the trip ………………… it was raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "in case",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7170cc992cf64df696efa3d058758945"
        }
    ]
}